ANTHONY JACOB KRUSO

Tony.kruso@gmail.com (937) 554-7389 116 Deer Creek Drive, Plainsboro NJ 08536

SUMMARY

Customer service expert with a wide range of skills and interests and the ability to get the job done under various circumstances. Experienced manager that has mentored people and gave them the necessary tools to advance their career, all while providing an enjoyable work environment and showcasing a strong work ethic.

EDUCATION

Fairmont High School Diploma 2008

EXPERIENCE

Cavalry Logistics; Weekend Team Leader Nashville, TN February 2015-August 2018

Team Leader for weekend staff. Responsible for delegating all duties, maintaining a positive and efficient work environment, and ensuring all customer freight is moving smoothly, while focusing on margin percentages and profitability. Part of a team of people that has doubled the revenue and margin for all freight moved over the weekend in a 4 month span.

PF Chang's; Server Nashville, Tennessee June 2014-September 2015

Member of the serving staff at PF Changs on West End Ave. in downtown Nashville. Constantly in competition for highest sales and tip percentage. Was next in line to start the process of becoming a trainer or manager to help new and old employees alike make a stronger and more efficient company.

Bailey's on Broadway; Head Cook Nashville, Tennessee. August 2013-January 2015

Head line cook for one of the top grossing Bailey's/Fox and Hound in the country. Highly respected and trusted member of the most popular sports bar on Broadway in downtown Nashville. Responsible for opening and closing duties while creating an efficient and pleasant work environment for front and back of house employees alike. I had only been a member of this company for a short time but had become the only employee that works front and back of house.

Elsa's Mexican Restaurant; Kitchen Manager Dayton, Ohio 2008-2011 & Lutz, Florida 2011-2013

As the head cook and kitchen manager of Elsa's Mexican Restaurant and Cantina I ensure superior customer service and an enjoyable workplace for all patrons. My additional responsibilities include serving and bartending while creating a more efficient and productive system for employees to better serve the customer.

SKILLS

- Serve Safe Manager certified.
- Customer Service Expert Key knowledge and experience in assisting the customer with all needs and requests while maintaining a professional demeanor.
- Hard Worker I never hesitate to jump in when someone needs help and am willing to do whatever it takes to accomplish the task at hand.
- Strong Communicator I communicate clearly and am skilled with negotiation.

^{*}references available upon request